bizpinion.com 2018-08-25

# Privacy Policy | Bizpinion

Privacy Policy

Last updated: 5.15.18

Bizpinion.com is a service provided by EMpanel Online Inc., a leader in market research.

EMpanel Online Inc., a leader in market research, endeavors to conform to the [CASRO](http://www.casro.org/codeofstandards.cfm) Code of Standards and Ethics for Survey Research and **_ALL_** relevant international regulations regarding privacy, including the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

We understand the need to have a formal privacy policy and are committed to protecting the privacy of our clients, panelists and visitors. We have therefore developed the following Privacy Policy which applies to EMpanel Online ([www.empanelonline.com](http://www.empanelonline.com/)), Bizpinion ([www.bizpinion.com](http://www.bizpinion.com/)), SurValidate (www.survalidate.com), and any current or future sites created or developed by EMpanel Online (collectively, “EOL”, “we”, or “us”). This Privacy Policy is further governed by our User Agreements specific to each product or service.

EMpanel Online Inc. assists firms in making better decisions through the use of information. We invite website visitors to join Research Communities of willing respondents and to express opinions on various topics.

**_We do not share, sell, rent or trade personally identifiable information with third parties for their promotional or marketing purposes.  _**

Personal Information

As used in this Policy, “personal information” means any information relating to an individual that can be used to identify that individual either on its own or in combination with other readily available data.

Information drives the research process. EOL gathers your personal and professional information upon registration to become part of our Research Community including, but not limited to, your demographics and career information. After registering we may ask members to provide us with additional personal information in order to invite them to appropriate opportunities. We require your email address in order that we can send you email invitations to participate in our upcoming research opportunities. The additional information we gather, such as your address, gender, birthday, and employment status, is used to match you with the appropriate market research projects.

Examples of Information Collected

The information we learn from data subjects helps us personalize and continually improve your experience. We respect your right to access, correct, request deletion or request restriction of our usage of your personal information as required by applicable law. We also take steps to ensure that the personal information we collect is accurate and up to date. Here are a few types of information that we collect and how it is used:

  1. _Information You Volunteer to Us and our Clients_

You provide most such information when you register and participate in our research projects. For example, you provide information when you complete a member profile or complete a questionnaire. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with information that enables us to connect you with projects that match your profile including, but not limited to: gender, birth date, income level, position of employment, industry employed, decision making authority and responsibilities, medical conditions. Financial information, including Social number or other tax IDs may be required for tax purposes in connection with incentive fulfillment in accordance to applicable laws.

  2. _E-mail Communications_

To help us make e-mail communication more useful and effective, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from us if your computer supports such capabilities.

  3. _Automatic Information_

We collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type, version, and time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system, and platform; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our website, including date and time; cookie number; projects you viewed. This information helps us to ensure your authenticity and prevent unwanted or fraudulent behavior.

  4. _Cookies_

When you visit EOL, we may send one or more cookies to your computer. Cookies are small files which are placed on your computer and allow us to perform analytics, operations of services and assessment of the usage of the Services – including but not limited to user preferences or trends (e.g., we may set a cookie on your browser allowing you to bypass engagement with an opportunity due to your previous participation). We use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to EOL. These persistent types of cookies can be removed. Each web browser implements different functionality, so please refer to the manuals or technical support resources that are available in conjunction with your web browser to learn the correct way to modify your cookies set-up. If you are using EOL in a jurisdiction where your prior consent is required for us to deploy any particular cookies, you will be asked to accept such cookies before they are deployed. If you elect to disable or reject cookies, some services may not function properly. By refusing cookies, you assume all responsibility of lacking or diminished functionality or associated benefits.

  5. _Mobile_

When you download our apps or those created by our subsidiaries, we may receive information about your location and your mobile device, including a unique identifier for your device. We may use this information to provide you with location-based opportunities, relevant to your location. Most mobile devices allow you to turn off location services. Enabled location services are not required to participate in our research opportunities.

  6. _Information from Other Sources_

Examples of information we receive from other sources include updated delivery and address information from our clients, subprocessors, or other third parties, which we use to correct our records and deliver your next opportunity or communication more accurately. We also use third party information to help prevent and detect fraud.

Information Retention and Accuracy

EOL makes efforts to ensure that personal information we receive, process, or maintain is accurate, complete, and reliable. We rely on the accuracy of the information provided directly to us but accept responsibility for the management and confidentiality of the personal information collected. In general, we keep personal information only as long as we need it to provide you the services you requested. We may also process data on behalf of third parties who have engaged us. We keep personal information processed on behalf of third parties for as long as needed to provide services to third party in question. However, we reserve the right to retain personal information for any period required by law or to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

Access and Correction

EOL believes you should be in control of your personal information. If at any time you wish to change the information you have provided to us, you may do so by logging in to your account and updating or deleting your personal information within the “My Account” section of the member website.

Data Protection and Security

It is imperative that you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to choose and maintain a secure password and to always sign off when you have finished with your session.

EOL employs reasonable security measures in an effort to prevent loss, misuse, and alteration of information under our control. We rely on various security procedures and systems to ensure the secure storage and transmission of data, including encryption and authentication technology licensed from third parties, to effect secure transmission of confidential information. However, we have absolutely no control over the security of other sites you might visit, interact with, or do business. We cannot guarantee the security of information on or transmitted via the Internet.

If we learn of a security systems breach, we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps, by posting a notice on EOL if a security and/or sending an email to you at the email address you have previously provided to us. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing.

Sharing Your Information

We may share information about you with third parties as follows:

  * with your consent;
  * with service providers who help deliver our services and run our business, subject to confidentiality agreements;
  * as required by law;
  * to protect you, our business, or third parties from harm, including but not limited to fraud and data security breaches;
  * in a reorganization or sale of our company or assets, subject to the acquirer accepting the commitments made in this Policy and in compliance with applicable law.

If we share your personal data with third party service providers and/or sub-processors, we will:

  * transfer such data only for limited and specified purposes;
  * require the sub-processor to provide at least the same level of privacy protection as is required by this Policy;
  * take reasonable and appropriate steps to ensure that the sub-processor effectively processes the personal data transferred in a manner consistent with the organization’s obligations under this Policy;
  * require the sub-processor to notify us if it determines it can no longer meet its obligation to provide the same level of protection as is required by this Policy;
  * upon notice, take reasonable and appropriate steps to stop and remediate unauthorized processing; and
  * provide a summary or a copy of the relevant privacy provisions of its contract with that sub-processor to the Department of Commerce upon request.

EOL shall remain liable under the EU-US Privacy Shield Principle of Accountability for Onward Transfer if its sub-processors process your personal information in a manner inconsistent with the Privacy Shield Principles, unless we prove we are not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage. If you are visiting this website from a country other than the country in which our servers are located, your communications with us will result in the transfer of information across international boundaries. By visiting this website and communicating electronically with us, you consent to such cross-border transfers.  In the case of data transfers from the EEA and Switzerland, the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks apply.

Children

Consistent with the federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we do not knowingly collect or solicit response data nor personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of thirteen (13). Any person who provides their personal information to EOL represents that they are 13 years of age or older. In the case you are a parent or legal guardian who discovers that your child has provided us with any of the foregoing, you may email contact[@bizpinion.com](mailto:dpo@empanelonline.com) to delete their information.

Transfer of Ownership

In the event that another company acquires some or all of the assets related to EOL, or if we experience some other change of control event such as insolvency, merger, bankruptcy or receivership, we reserve the right to include any or all Personal Information among the assets transferred to the acquiring company. EOL will commit the surviving entity in the case of a merger, or the acquiring entity in the case of an acquisition or sale, to agree in writing to protect and maintain the security and integrity of the transferred Personal Information in accordance with any applicable laws. Any entity receiving such information in connection with any of these transactions must comply with all the terms of this Privacy Policy, unless advanced notice has been provided to EOL members.

Choice/Opt-Out

Participation in our research communities and all survey invitations are always voluntary. A member can always willingly not participate in a particular opportunity or terminate their membership. If a panel member desires to end his or her membership with EOL, such panel member may terminate their membership by (a) following the instructions set forth in their membership account, (b) sending an email request to [contact@bizpinion.com](mailto:contact@empanelonline.com) from the email address associated with their membership, or (c) selecting the opt-out link contained in each email invitation sent to members of our research communities and following the applicable steps.  Regardless of the method used, opting out deactivates the member’s account and terminates their membership (including all redemption reward points earned). EOL will then deactivate the applicable membership account and the individual will not receive any further opportunities.

Do Not Track

Some browsers have a “do not track” feature that lets you tell websites you do not want to have your online activities tracked. Because these features are not yet uniform, we do not presently respond to “do not track” signals.

Customer Information

We may collect employee contact names, addresses, phone numbers, and email addresses of our business partners, including buyers, suppliers, and vendors, for the administration of our business relationships. To opt-out of business-related email campaigns, (a) send an email request to [contact@bizpinion.com](mailto:contact@empanelonline.com) from the associated email address or (b) selecting the opt-out link contained in each email and following the subsequent steps.

Future Updates to this Privacy Policy

EMpanel Online Inc. reserves the right, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at our discretion at any time for any reason. With any changes to the Privacy Policy, we will display a “last updated” date found at the top of this Privacy Policy.

By agreeing to participate, you signify your acceptance of the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. When we do update the Privacy Policy, we will inform you of these changes and we will revise the “last modified” date at the top of this Privacy Policy to alert. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy. Your continued participation constitutes your acceptance of a revised Privacy Policy, as amended.

Contact Information

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you can contact us by e-mail, direct mail or telephone:

Mailing Address:

**EMpanel Online Inc.  
**Attn: Privacy Concern  
6017 Catamaran Court  
Flowery Branch, GA 30542 USA

E-Mail: [contact@bizpinion.com](mailto:contact@empanelonline.com)

Phone: +1 (678) 390-5177
